<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AlmondWhite</title>
    <description>A blog on all things interesting</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/AlmondWhite/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/AlmondWhite/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 21:17:35 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 21:17:35 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the first post!
So this is a little project I’m putting together initially as a test but hopefully something I can grow in to a justifiable site. I hope to talk about all things
weird or interesting, in a way that won’t bore or drone on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog is built on Jekyll, a new framework I’m trying as it appears to make updating and maintaining a site like this facile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve had many sites in the past, all of which were manually created from the ground up, and as such, adding new posts or updating elements takes a toll on time and 
effort. Considering the time it takes to write a post or article, update a page template, and new custom stylings and then link that page and ensure it resolves correctly is a pain in the ass. As far as I have experienced with Jekyll, it;s simply a matter of dropping a new .md file in the respective folder and im done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope to make this project an interesting one and see how it goes from there. I’ve also set up a &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/AlmondWhite&quot;&gt;new twitter account&lt;/a&gt; to update about posts and articles while I get the RSS and subsription features up for those who are interested. More to come, thanks for stopping by!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/AlmondWhite/2019/first-post/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/AlmondWhite/2019/first-post/</guid>
        
        <category>blog news</category>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
